[theme music playing]
So, did you check on him
since he just got out of jail?
Did you sleep with him?
I'll do everything I can to stop him.
-As long as it keeps him away from you!
-Arnaldo!
Arnaldo!
[Julio] What's happening to you?
You should focus on Emilia.
Use her, so that you can get
all of the Ardientes' wealth.
[Raul] Don't worry about Emilia.
I'm already working on it.
Pills? I don't need this. I'm not crazy!
[Julio] Just take the medication.
[Ivy] I'll rob you
of your sanity, Arnaldo.
I won't leave a shred of it.
I'll make you lose your mind
to the point that you'll beg for death.
ARNALDO, CONFESS YOUR SINS…
Who sent this?!
Don't take them off until
you hear Arnaldo going berserk.
Are… Are you seeing this?
What are you doing?!
Are you taking a video of me?!
[Emilia] Ever since
you became his fiancée…
-he's started acting crazy!
-That's enough!
I'm not crazy!
I'm the mayor of this town
and soon-to-be governor.
Nothing will change.
You won't attend the debate!
You'll only make a fool
of yourself, Arnaldo!
Listen to me! I am still your mother!
Diego Torillo for a new Ardiente!
Viva Ardiente!
[man 1] Mayor Arnaldo's throwing
a fit outside.
His huge poster got vandalized
with the word murderer on it.
[Julio] Emilia. Emilia, answer your phone.
We cannot jeopardize Arnaldo's win.
Emilia--
[Jaguar] I really want to dance with you.
But on one condition.
[woman] You may now go to the front,
Mayor Arnaldo Ardiente-Torillo.
Mr. Diego Ardiente-Torillo.
[supporters cheering]
I want you to cancel everything.
I'm sorry, but I can't, Congressman!
What do you mean you can't? Huh? Hey!
I'll pay for all your expenses,
if that's what you're worried about.
And please, don't test my patience!
Because if you insist
on having it your way,
I won't let my grandson go there!
You will never see
Arnaldo Ardiente-Torillo!
-Congressman--
-Shut up!
Can't you understand--
You know, you should be thankful
I'm not feeling well,
or else I would be there.
And if I were there, you'd be
kneeling in front of me!
Remember this…
When Julio Ardiente tells you
to do something, you do it!
Yes, Congressman.
-Diego Torillo! Diego Torillo!
-Arnaldo! Arnaldo! Arnaldo!
Kate, please tell Mayor
the debate is canceled.
Okay? Go to him now.
Diego Torillo!
[no audible dialogue]
Mayor, the debate's been canceled.
[clears throat]
Hon, why? What happened?
[Arnaldo] I… I don't know.
What's happening?
Mayor, we are sorry.
We have to cancel the debate.
This is unprofessional. He's ready.
We apologize.
It's the congressman's orders.
Grandpa canceled it. He doesn't trust me.
He doesn't have faith in me.
I know, hon.
I'm shocked to learn your grandfather…
-feels that way.
-He doesn't have faith in me.
But, hon…
Arnaldo, you need to go through with this.
If I were you, I'd push through
with the debate.
Because I trust you.
You need to go through with it.
It's not your grandfather
who'll embarrass himself
if you won't go through
with this, you will.
So, if I were you, Arnaldo, I'd do it.
I… I… I understand.
But there must be a reason
why he wanted it canceled,
so let's find out. Let's find out.
-Let's find out.
-Hon, go through with it.
Don't you want to?
No. There must be a reason…
Let's find out. Let's find out.
-Let's… let's find out.
-So, you're canceling it?
Let's find out.
-Okay.
-Let's find out.
Let's find out.
-Let's find out--
-Mamita.
-Let's find out.
-Let's go.
Let's find out.
Let's find out. Let's find out.
[woman] What happened?
[tense music playing]
[Kate] We are very sorry to announce
that the debate will not push through.
[crowd murmuring]
[supporters clamoring]
[unintelligible]
[clamoring]
Miss, excuse me.
We're ready for the debate. What happened?
Sorry, ma'am. There was an emergency.
The congressman had the debate canceled.
Okay, thank you.
Everyone!
Julio Ardiente had the debate canceled.
I'm sure they want
to protect Arnaldo's image
because Diego will reveal
all of their darkest secrets.
-That's right!
-That's right! Yeah!
[Loring] Typical! Just when we were ready!
[Diego] Friends!
If they can be silenced by the Ardientes,
we'll stand our ground.
We shouldn't be afraid.
We should fight back
and unite for justice!
[man] Down with the Ardientes!
[crowd] Take them down! Take them down!
Bring down the Ardientes! Take them down!
Take them down! Bring down the Ardientes!
[instrumental music playing]
[distorted voice] Emilia.
I can't wait for you to be mine.
[Emilia exhales and groans]
Enough!
You know, I appreciate that
I feel so loved and valued now.
But this is not enough.
Why don't we join forces, then?
Come with me, Emilia.
Jaguar. The offer you made me
isn't enough to convince me
to join forces with you
and abandon my father.
[tense music playing]
And by the way, next time…
it's your turn to be tied up.
Arnaldo forcefully sent me
to prison without a trial.
But now I'm free.
I won't back down.
The Ardientes will do everything
just to get what they want!
They'll push us into a corner!
They'll threaten.
But we shouldn't let them scare us.
We won't stop
until the truth is in our hands!
-That's right.
-Correct.
That's right, Miss Camia.
It's time for us to fight.
Let's put an end
to the tyranny of the Ardientes!
-That's right!
-[applause]
Diego! Diego! For real change!
Diego Torillo for real change!
[ominous music playing]
I KNOW THE TRUTH ABOUT IVY AGUAS.
[phone ringing]
Hello?
Now then, tell me
everything there is to know
about the woman we know as Ivy Aguas.
[suspenseful music playing]
Aguas.
-Have a seat, ma'am.
-Thank you.
Thank you.
[phone ringing]
Yes, Emilia?
-Ivy!
-Can I help you?
Where are you? Can we meet?
I'll come see you, okay?
[suspenseful music playing]
Bye!
Ivy, Ivy Aguas… Too many secrets!
-They're in trouble now.
-We'll show them all.
We'll get our revenge.
-[laughter]
-[indistinct chatter]
Mr. Diego, this is our chance.
[Diego's supporter] Yes.
[laughs] Do the honors, Mr. Diego.
JULIO THE HEADHUNTER
EMILIA THE LIAR
ARNALDO THE CLOWN
[screams]
Insolent bastards!
-For a new Ardiente!
-What are you doing?!
-What's happening?
What are you doing?! Stop that!
-What are you doing?!
Diego Torillo for the new Ardiente!
Oust the Ardientes!
Diego Torillo for a new Ardiente!
[Ardiente's supporter crying]
-How could you!?
-How dare you do this!
…for a new Ardiente!
Diego Torillo!
Diego Torillo for a new Ardiente!
-[Ardiente's supporter wailing]
-Let's go!
[Ardiente's supporter wailing]
Why did you do that?!
[tense music playing]
[screams]
Hello, where the hell is Arnaldo?
Tell him to come see me!
As for the other,
make that bastard suffer!
I want Diego Torillo's head!
Hi, Emilia! Please sit down.
No need.
I am so surprised
you are not with my beloved son.
It's too bad…
I wanted him to hear
everything I found about you…
Ivy Aguas.
But it doesn't matter. This can't wait.
[sighs]
So, you've come up with another issue.
And here I was hoping
for a nice quiet night.
But then, since you're here,
I doubt that's going to happen.
Okay, no more mind games, then.
I know the truth about your identity.
I know all your secrets, Ivy Aguas!
Oh.
Emilia, haven't you dispatched
your private investigator yet?
Stop it already.
You're just making things worse
with what you're doing.
Please stop it.
My men have your adoption
papers signed by Prianka Aguas!
She just picked you off from the streets!
Am I right? Or am I just too right?!
Who are you, really?
Who are you, Ivy Aguas?!
Since you came to this province,
you ruined everything!
You misled my family
and everyone in this town!
Now tell me…
Who are you, really?
Are you Lily Cruz?!
[dramatic music]
[tense music swelling]
I've got a gut feeling
that you're Lily Cruz!
Just admit that you're Lily Cruz!
Are you Lily Cruz?!
[woman] No she isn't!
[pensive music playing]
This is the end of your search
for Lily Cruz, Emilia Ardiente!
[tense music playing]
And who are you?
I'm right in front of you!
I am Lily Cruz!
The one and only Lily Cruz!
Is this a joke?! [laughs]
You're Lily Cruz? But she's Lily Cruz!
You might be tough.
Rich and brutal.
But you're so easy to fool,
Emilia Ardiente.
You're wasting your time throwing tantrums
when you should be paying
for your crimes against me!
Because I am Lily Cruz!
[tense music playing]
-You're a liar!
-Emilia!
Emilia!
You work for Lily Cruz! Huh?
Don't touch me!
You're right.
So, don't think of harming us, Emilia.
Because this whole place?
It's surrounded by our men!
Well, Emilia Ardiente…
You look like you've seen a ghost!
Now that the person you've been
looking for is in front of you.
Are you scared?
No. No!
You poisoned my father.
You had my mother raped,
and you wanted me dead!
But too bad for you
I'm not a ghost, Emilia.
Because I'm alive! Very much alive!
[Emilia] No.
You're a liar! You're lying! Liar!
Are you scared? Are you trembling?
Haven't you been looking for me?
Now that I'm here, I will bury you alive!
[tense music playing]
And she's back!
Lily Cruz really is alive.
Emilia…
Emilia, please don't pass out.
[tense music continues]
[Julio] You need to break up
with Ivy Aguas.
Or else…
you will lose this election.
Grandpa, didn't we talk
about this already?
Think hard about it.
Think very hard.
You killed because of Ivy Aguas.
You framed Diego because of Ivy Aguas.
You forget that I'm an Ardiente!
I may love Ivy,
but I never forget who I am.
I'm a predator.
A predator?
Or a kitten pretending to be a lion?
Is that what you think of me now?
That's why you halted the debate?
The election hasn't begun
and you're already
putting a nail in my coffin.
How could you? You know what?
All my life…
All my life, I've been following
your orders, Grandpa.
Now, I disobey you one time,
just one time, for my happiness.
For Ivy. And now you think I'm trash?
Well, I'm not surprised.
You only love me because
I've been obedient to you.
I'm the one you can control.
I'm the only one you can control.
I'm the only one you can control…
I'm the only one you
can control… Stop. Stop.
My beloved grandson…
Believe it or not, I have never
loved anybody in my life…
more than I have loved you.
Jepoy, what is Anna doing here
in Poblacion Ardiente?
I missed you so much, Lily.
You love me because I'm
the only one you can control.
I will control you if I have to, Arnaldo.
Because you are the sole heir
to the power of the Ardientes.
An Ardiente should be the only
one to rule Poblacion Ardiente.
And your failure is not an option.
I thought we wouldn't make it.
Thank you for that. But, Anna…
What's happening, Jepoy?
Why do you have to pretend to be me?
To help you, Lily.
I'm not Lily anymore.
It's Ivy Aguas now.
You should call me Ivy.
I'm sorry. I just got used to…
I know everything. Jepoy told me--
Of course Jepoy told you everything.
Seriously, Jepoy?
We've talked about this, remember?
No one else can know about my secret
because I wanted to keep it between us.
No one else will get involved.
And now you told Anna?
Ivy, believe me. I tried my best to--
It was my decision to help you, Ivy.
Didn't we make a promise?
That, whatever happens,
we won't abandon one another?
-One for all.
-All for one.
Together forever.
-One for all.
-All for one.
-Together…
-[all] forever!
Yay!
I haven't forgotten that promise.
But, Anna…
Anna, it's so dangerous… for you.
But we got Emilia Ardiente
to believe I'm Lily Cruz, right?
Anna, believe me.
There's no way to make sure
that monster believes
you really are Lily Cruz.
Anna, I won't allow you to get hurt.
I don't know what I would do if…
if the Ardientes hurt you too.
So, please…
Jepoy, take Anna away from here.
Take her back home.
Lily…
Ivy.
I won't abandon you.
Anna, thank you.
But you have no business
being in Poblacion Ardiente.
Listen to me.
Ivy, I know everything.
Those Ardientes ruined your life.
But you're not the only one
who lost a loved one.
Aunt Carlotta was like a mother to me too.
Please don't deny me the chance
to seek justice for her death.
[suspenseful music playing]
[grunts]
I'm Lily Cruz!
Now that I'm here,
[echoing] I will bury you alive!
Lily Cruz. Lily Cruz.
This is not happening. Come on.
Emilia, think. Think. Lily Cruz.
[dishes clatter]
Ouch!
[exclaims]
Get out of my sight!
You're such an idiot!
[screams]
-[exhales sharply]
-[Julio] Emilia!
Why are you screaming like a cat in heat?
What's wrong with you? Well?
What!?
-Papa…
-What?
-Lily Cruz is back.
You heard me, Papa.
I said Lily Cruz is back.
In the flesh.
[suspenseful music swelling]
Emilia.
If this is one of
your episodes of paranoia,
then just sit down
and pass out on the couch…
because no one here
is willing to catch you.
No, Papa.
I'm not paranoid and, this time,
I'm telling the truth.
I saw her with my two eyes, Papa.
I saw her! She's alive.
She's back. And guess who?
With whom, Papa?! Madrigal!
So, that guy's been playing us all along.
[ominous music playing]
This isn't just your fight, Ivy.
I lost a foster mother
because of Arnaldo Ardiente.
I owe so much to Aunt Carlotta, Ivy.
She raised me when my parents died.
That's why I have to make
Arnaldo Ardiente pay.
You can't.
Anna, you will go back home.
You have no idea just what
the Ardientes are capable of.
-Ivy. I don't care.
-You can't!
I'll do this whether you like it or not,
with or without your permission.
I won't let them do to you
what they did to Nanny Carlotta.
You're leaving, Anna.
You will listen to me
whether you like it or not.
It's for your own good, Anna.
It's for your own good.
Are you sure?
So, you mean to tell me…
that while that rat Madrigal was away,
they were actually preparing
for Lily Cruz's comeback?
Yes, Papa. Yes.
That stinking bloodsucking leech!
Yes, Papa. And guess what?
I found out from my private investigator…
that Ivy Aguas was adopted.
So, there are two things now.
Number one, she's a liar.
Number two, she must be the real Lily Cruz
because she's been
hiding her real identity!
When will you leave Ivy alone?
The real Lily Cruz
already revealed herself,
but you still won't leave Ivy alone?!
That's what our family is good at.
We're experts at sabotaging our own.
No, Arnaldo.
I will never let her become an Ardiente.
Because she has so many secrets,
and, until I uncover them all,
I won't leave your whore alone!
[exclaims]
I would like to see you try!
So, you'll feel this knife…
-Papa!
-Arnaldo!
…run through your chest.
And I'll see you in hell.
Because I'll follow you.
It's only a matter of time
before this old man joins us.
See! One big, happy family in hell!
-Arnaldo!
-I say let's start now!
[Emilia exclaims] Papa!
[Julio] Put that blade down!
Look at me! Look at me!
This old man, whom you refer to…
is the man who made you!
I am the man who created you!
I am the man who gave you brains!
I am the man who put you in power!
So, get rid of this knife, and don't ever…
ever try to scare me
with your little antics.
Look at us! Huh?
Is this what you want?! This?!
You want us to murder each other
all because of a small problem?!
The enemy is using
elementary tactics on us!
The art of war!
Divide and conquer!
Keep this in mind.
Even if there's a problem…
even if we have issues with each other,
we never turn on family!
Blood is thicker and should always be
thicker than water.
We have this province in our hands…
And it should stay that way.
We own Ardiente!
And we should stick together!
No one… No one
takes the power away from us!
You put that in your thick heads.
[Camia] Please, come in!
-Nice house, Ma'am Camia.
-Are you all hungry?
Famished. Oh, wait, let me help you.
I'm going to help too!
I'm clueless, but I'll help too!
-Where's the kitchen?
-Make yourselves at home!
-Yeah, where's the kitchen?
-I might just lie down here…
-to feel at home.
-[chuckles]
Oh, Mr. Pandoy!
You're going down, Arnaldo.
Your reign over this town
will soon be over.
Soon…
this province will be freed
from your family's deadly grip.
This is all your fault, Papa!
See?
You just created a monster in Arnaldo!
He almost killed me!
His own mother!
Papa… And that's unforgivable!
I'm sorry to say this, Papa,
but Diego will win this election!
Is that what you think?!
Is that what you believe?
If so, we start moving heaven and earth
to make sure that Arnaldo
still comes out on top!
At any cost!
You're going help Arnaldo cheat?!
After what he did to me?!
-You can do that for him?!
-Yes!
Because your best,
and everybody else's best…
is still Arnaldo's worst!
Arnaldo is the only hope we have…
in making sure we maintain
our family's power.
And after that,
we deal with Ivy Aguas
and all our enemies.
In the meantime,
look for that retard, Madrigal.
And find wherever this Lily Cruz is.
Send her back to whatever
hellhole she crawled out from!
We are not going to lose this town.
Bunch of scatterbrains!
Ivy's just like that because
she wants to protect you.
After everything you've been
through helping her,
you still take her side?
Anna, I'm not taking any sides here.
I want to visit Aunt Carlotta.
Anna, we've talked about this, right?
I said I want to pay
Aunt Carlotta a visit.
I know you want to visit her too.
[instrumental theme music playing]
Ivy, I know everything.
Those Ardientes ruined your life.
But you're not the only one
who lost a loved one.
Aunt Carlotta was like a mother to me too.
Please don't deny me the chance
to seek justice for her death.
[young Jepoy] I really like it here.
It's not like Manila.
But you'll still leave me here
because you're going back
to Manila when school starts.
Don't worry.
I'll just ask Miss Prianka
to come back here
for our vacation next year.
-Let's go there.
-Let's go.
Hello.
Wait!
Aunt Carlotta might be looking for me.
Hey! She's our Nanny Carlotta.
What do you mean?
Well… She looks after us too.
Are you Nanny Carlotta's niece?
Miss Prianka told me about her.
Aunt Carlotta asked me to stay with her.
She said she'd take care of me.
My mom already passed away.
And so did my dad.
Me too. Both my parents are gone.
Well, I'm an orphan too.
But we all have our Nanny Carlotta!
Right. So, don't be sad.
I'm the parking boy, Jepoy!
Hey, you're not a parking boy
because you're not
in the parking lot anymore.
You're now called goat boy, Jepoy!
Since we're on a farm!
Didn't Nanny Carlotta ask
you to take care of the goats?
By the way, I'm Lily.
What's your name?
I'm Anna. That's my name.
Do you want to go to Nanny Carlotta now?
Come with us! Come on, Anna!
-Hurry!
-Let's find Nanny Carlotta!
[pensive music playing]
[young Lily] Let go of me!
Let go of me!
[whistles]
If you're in trouble, blow this.
I'm the parking boy! Jepoy!
The cops! Run!
[police officer] You two, chase
after them! Stand up!
[young Lily] Here, eat up.
You're like an angel.
[Arnaldo] This is Madrigal.
My most trusted man.
He'll accompany us.
[Ivy] You find yourself in peril
because you're one of Arnaldo's men,
but you still continue to help me.
Ivy.
Jepoy.
I'm happy to see you again, Jepoy.
When you left Poblacion Ardiente,
I didn't know what happened to you.
I didn't know where to find you,
so, now, I'm happy to see you
safe and sound.
Didn't I promise you I wouldn't
leave no matter what happens?
So, I need to stay alive to protect you.
Thank you, Jepoy.
Thank you for everything.
While I was away, it was Anna
who nursed me back to health.
Although it was hard for me,
I had to tell her everything.
[soft piano music playing]
I'm sorry.
That's how we found out Emilia
was looking for the real Lily,
so we began preparing.
We waited, hidden in the shadows.
We waited for the perfect opportunity
to reveal Anna as the real Lily.
Jepoy, we had an agreement.
We wouldn't drag anyone else into this.
Why did you tell Anna? Why her?
Of all people… You know
how important Anna is to us.
And you told her?
What did you expect me to do?
She insisted. What could I have done?
Where is she? Where are you staying now?
We're staying at a safe house.
Actually, the real reason why I'm here is
I want to ask you something.
Sure. What is it?
If it's okay, we'd like
to visit Nanny Carlotta.
[somber piano music playing]
All right. Everything's ready, let's eat.
-Diego, sit over there.
-We're coming.
Yes, Auntie.
-Veggies.
-Yummy!
-I'll sit here.
-Sit over here.
Nanny, Uncle, Aunt Camia, Batch…
I just want to say thank you.
Because from the moment
I got arrested until I got out,
you were always there for me.
-Of course.
-You never left my side.
Thank you for all your love and support.
Well, we won't stop trying
to show the people
that we're in the right.
I know.
And no matter what happens,
we will continue to try our best
to take down the Ardientes.
That's right. And we should
also continue eating!
-Why are you so serious?
-We're just hungry.
We might need to go to the hospital.
[instrumental theme music playing]
Nanny.
Nanny, I miss you so much.
Every day…
I miss you, Nanny.
Nanny, you have visitors.
Jepoy is here. And Anna too.
But, Nanny, please help me.
Help me try to…
convince them not to
push through with their plans.
Nanny, I don't want them to get hurt.
I hope they'll listen to me.
[weeping]
Auntie…
Nanny, I couldn't protect you.
[weeping]
[instrumental theme music playing]
[music fades]
-[young Lily] Come and get me!
-[young Anna] Hurry!
[Carlotta] Hey! Lily, come here!
Dear, come here!
-Who is it?!
-Lily, dear!
[young Jepoy] You're it!
[young Lily] She caught me.
[Carlotta] Are you all hungry?
-[young Lily] Starving!
-[Carlotta] Okay.
[young Lily] What's that?
[inaudible]
-[Carlotta] Just keep eating.
-[young Lily] Let's eat first.
Go ahead. Come on.
Here's your spoon. Let's eat, Nanny!
[Carlotta] I'll eat later. You go ahead.
-Have some bananas.
-Nanny, here's the knife!
[Carlotta] Oh, dear! Let's eat.
[Carlotta giggling]
-[young Lily] You're it!
-[young Anna] What?!
[young Lily] Nanny, you're it!
-[Carlotta] Oh.
-[young Lily] You're it, Nanny.
[young Lily] You're it!
[Carlotta laughing]
[Carlotta] I'm it? But I wasn't playing!
[Anna weeping]
[sobs]
[sobbing]
[Arnaldo] You're worried I'll lose too.
[Julio] Yes. Don't give me
that surprised look.
Because you know I'm right!
You allowed your emotions
to rule over that thick head of yours.
[Anna] Why will you marry that monster?
[Ivy] You need to trust my plans.
Don't try to stop my wedding
or any of my plans.
Don't you dare.
-I'm not weak.
-You're helpless!
Take back what you said!
You don't want Ivy
to marry Arnaldo, either.
You already know my answer to that.
It's time to stop pretending.
You should have revealed yourself.
[theme music playing]